<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Aswin Natesh</title><link>https://aswinnatesh.com/</link><description>Recent content on Aswin Natesh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 08:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aswinnatesh.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Beyond the Crystals</title><link>https://aswinnatesh.com/posts/incredible-india/beyond-the-crystals/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 08:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aswinnatesh.com/posts/incredible-india/beyond-the-crystals/</guid><description>Capturing the lives of Marakkanam’s salt pan workers. Close to Pondicherry, on the section of the East Coast Road that connects the city with Chennai, a fascinating and unusual landscape captures the attention of passersby. Upon getting closer to the fields, one is blinded by the brightness of the scorching sun, and within minutes, one’s throat becomes parched. These are the circumstances under which the salt pan workers of Marakkanam, Tamil Nadu labour.</description></item><item><title>Uniquely Chettinad</title><link>https://aswinnatesh.com/posts/incredible-india/uniquely-chettinad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 08:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aswinnatesh.com/posts/incredible-india/uniquely-chettinad/</guid><description>Chettinad houses are a blend of colonial architecture and palace style houses with traditional architectural styles used dexterously with European groove and influences from various other parts of the world. This became possible because of the extensive travel undertaken by the Chettiars on business trips. Extensive woodwork made of Burmese teak wood, the attractive black and white imported Italian tiles for the lengthy hallways and the other decorative items such as the unique British style lamp shades were used elaborately.</description></item><item><title>Kolam | Lifestyle &amp; Culture</title><link>https://aswinnatesh.com/posts/incredible-india/kolam-lifestyle-culture/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 08:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aswinnatesh.com/posts/incredible-india/kolam-lifestyle-culture/</guid><description>Kolam – The Traditional Floor Drawing of South India Kolam is a drawing generally drawn at the entrance of a house or any other building. This is a very old practice in South India. Dried rice flour or other types of white powders are used for drawing kolams. Although there are numerous traditional kolam patterns and lot more can be created depending on the creativity of the person who draws it, it is not drawn like a picture.</description></item></channel></rss>